Guide to the Stanford University, Humanities Honors Program, Theses
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2010-072
  - Murdock, Malcolm, Discarding the Bard: Self-reflexive thematic subversion in Laurence Olivier's 'Henry V'., 2006 (Box 3)
  - Okanlami, Oluwaferanmi O., Narrative: The Bridge between the Kingdom of the Well and the Kingdom of the Ill. (Box 3)
  - Palumbo-Liu, Fabrice, The Use of Judicial Farce in 'Maitre Pathelin'., 2007 (Box 3)
  - Peretti, Conner G., Witness to the Infernal: William Blake's sacramental 'Marriage' and reading as a redemptive act., 2009 (Box 3)
  - Rabedeau, Jennifer, Seduction: Representations of the fallen woman in the early works of Frances Burney and Jane Austen. (Box 3)
  - Salisbury, Katie Anne, Imagining China: american perceptions of the Chinese through 1930s Cinema. (Box 3)
  - Snyder, Sara, The Grief Memoir: conceptualizing authorship through the lens of spirituality: C.S. Lewis and Isabel Allende., 2010 (Box 3)
  - Sylvester, Carlyn, The Power of the Joke, The Joke of Power: A study of humor and marginality in the United States., 2009 (Box 3)
  - Tonelli, Alyssa Luna, "Fat and Beautiful!" The Real Women in 'Real Women Have Curves'., 2008 (Box 3)
  - Trotter, Emma, In The Blood: The genealogy, aesthetics, and politics of Native American fiction., 2010 (Box 3)
  - Wertheimer, Samuel, Doctrines for Doctors: Prescriptions for physicians' emotions in 'Madame Bovary' and 'Love in the Time of Cholera'., 2007 (Box 3)
  - Williamson, Alexander Leland, Separating the Strands: Chogyam Trungpa's Buddhist and Shambhala teachings., 2008 (Box 3)
  - Wilson, Douglas, The Legend of Zelda: The Wind Waker: From videogame to virtual playground and beyond., 2007 (Box 3)
  - Wyman, Anne Julie, I Think of You Often: A history of International PEN as seen through the organization's relationship with the writers Miguel de Unamuno, Ernst Toller and Vaclav Havel., 2008 (Box 3)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2011-152
  - Avila, Tanya Lynn, Mississippi freedom summer: foundations and transformations revealed in history and autobiography., 2003 (Box 1)
  - Coffman, Matt, Dark matters: death, language and human limitation in British First World War poetry., 2001 (Box 1)
  - Hutcherson, Miri, The force of repetition in Genesis 1, Mantra and Blessingway., 2003 (Box 1)
  - Miaw, Calvin, Language and politics in the poetry of Kathy Dee Kaleokealoha Kaloloahilani Banggo and the drama of Alani Apio., 2003 (Box 1)
  - Ormseth, Maren E., The significance of artistic affirmation in Nietzche and Joyce., 1987 (Box 1)
  - Scheirer, Kevin, Nixon in Guatemala: photographic narratives of the political theater., 2003 (Box 1)
  - Groban, Joshua, The distance from humanity: human radiation experiments in America., 1995 (Box 1)
  - Shepherd, Hana, The fair and welfare/warfare: representations of nationhood and defense in poverty policy., 2004 (Box 1)
  - Wang, Margaret, Little orphan dandies: how Oscar Wilde and Evelyn Waugh "redress" their fathers., 1994 (Box 1)
  - Evangelista, Cecilia Luz, Kundera and Konwicki, and the interior world of the postwar East European intellectual., 1988 (Box 1)
  - Banks, Miranda Janis, Sunset Boulevard: myth, stardom, and the hyper-reel., 1994 (Box 1)
  - Schoellner, Karsten, An aesthetic portrait of Stephen Dedalus: epiphany and idolatry., 2000 (Box 1)
  - McCrudden, Ian C., The phenomenon of the voice and the listening "I": the subject in Beckett's later prose and drama., 1994 (Box 2)
  - Lim, Sandra, Double-consciousness and the protean self in Sylvia Plath's Ariel., 1995 (Box 2)
  - Hughes, Jennifer, Orlando: novel & film; form and the construction of gender., 1995 (Box 2)
  - Forner, Sean, Totalitarianism in literature: freedom and domination in twentieth-century dystopian fiction., 1995 (Box 2)
  - Romanska, Magda, Playing with the void: dance macabre of object and subject in the bio-objects of T. Kantor's Theater of Death., 1998 (Box 2)
  - Slate, Nico, Where nothing needs to be said: Heidegger, Walden, and the "Odas Elementales" of Pablo Neruda., 2002 (Box 2)
  - Jung, Gregory, The greatest enemy oif all: the life and struggles of Henry Miller., 1994 (Box 2)